Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Mitchell, Allan C. G., 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 395)
  - Mitchell, Allan C. G., 1939-1962; (17 folders) (Box 396)
  - Mitchell, Effie Myrtle, 1937-1938 (Box 396)
  - Mitchell, Hall or Annex for Animal House, 1939-1940 (Box 396)
  - Mitchell, Hall, 1942-1943 (Box 396)
  - Mo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 396)
  - Moenkhaus, Prof. W.J., 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 396)
  - Moffatt, Prof. J.E., 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 396)
  - Moffatt, Prof. J.E., 1941-1953; (12 folders) (Box 397)
  - Moh, 1937-1961; (24 folders) (Box 397)
  - Mol, 1948-1949 (Box 397)
  - Molecular Biology, 1958-1959 (Box 397)
  - Mon, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 397)
  - Monon Railway Company, 1937-1959; (6 folders) (Box 397)
  - Monroe County Fair, 1953-1957 (Box 397)
  - Monroe County Unit of the Women's Field Army for the Control of Cancer, 1938-1939 (Box 397)
  - Monroe Reservoir, 1961-1962 (Box 397)
  - Moo, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 397)
  - Moo, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 398)
  - Moor, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 398)
  - Moore, 1949-1955; (7 folders) (Box 398)
  - Moore, Harold E., 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 398)
  - Moore, Harold E., 1943-1953; (10 folders) (Box 399)
  - Moore Noble, 1940-1941 (Box 399)
  - Mor, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 399)
  - Morg, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 399)
  - Morgan, Prof. W.T., 1938-1939 (Box 399)
  - Morgenthau, Dr. Hans J., 1938-1940 (Box 399)
  - Morr, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 399)
  - Morr, 1948-1962; (14 folders) (Box 400)
  - Morris, Dwight H., 1949-1961 (Box 400)
  - Morris James M. (Lt. Colonnel), 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 400)
  - Morrison, Guy E., 1938-1939 (Box 400)
  - Mortgage Conference, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 400)
  - Mos, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 400)
  - Mossholder, Robert L., 1952-1959; (7 folders) (Box 400)
  - Mother's Day, 1941-1942 (Box 400)
  - Motion Picture Committee, 1941-1943; (2 folders) (Box 400)
  - Mott, George Fox, 1937-1938 (Box 400)
  - Mottier, Dr. D.M. Property, 1938-1939 (Box 400)
  - Mou, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 400)
  - Moy, Seong, 1952-1953 (Box 400)
  - Mu, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 400)
  - Mu, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 401)
  - Mueller, John H., 1942-1953; (11 folders) (Box 401)
  - Mueller, Kate H. (Box 401)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 401)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 401)
    - 1941-1953, (16 folders) (Box 401)
  - Muhler, Joseph Charles (Box 401)
    - 1943-1953 (Box 401)
    - 1954-1961 (Box 401)
  - Mul, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 401)
  - Mul, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 402)
  - Muller, Herman J., 1945-1962; (7 folders) (Box 402)
  - Munro, Edna (Box 402)
    Director, Physical Education for Women
    - 1937-1938 (Box 402)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 402)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 402)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 402)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 402)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 402)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 402)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 402)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 402)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 402)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 402)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 402)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 402)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 402)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 402)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 402)
    - 1953-1956 (Box 402)
  - Mur, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 402)
  - Muralist for New Building, 1939-1940 (Box 402)
  - Murphy, Duncan, 1954-1958 (Box 402)
  - Murphy, Everett, 1949-1950; (2 folders) (Box 402)
  - Murr, 1937-1960; (23 folders) (Box 402)
  - Murr, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 403)
  - Murray, John J., 1950-1954 (Box 403)
  - Museum, 1958-1959; (3 folders) (Box 403)
  - School of Music, 1948-1962; (22 folders) (Box 403)
  - Museum Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 403)
  - Museum Project, 1938-1939 (Box 403)
  - School of Music, 1937-1957; (57 folders) (Box 403)
  - School of Music, 1956-1962; (26 folders) (Box 404)
  - Music Clinic, 1946-1954 (Box 404)
  - Music Series, 1938-1943; (5 folders) (Box 404)
  - Music Teachers Conference, 1944-1945 (Box 404)
  - My, 1937-1962; (11 folders) (Box 404)
  - Myers, 1941-1955; (14 folders) (Box 404)
  - Myers, Dean Emeritus B.D., 1937-1944; (8 folders) (Box 404)
  - Myers, Dean B.D., 1940-1952; (12 folders) (Box 405)
  - N, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 405)
  - Najam, Edward W., 1955-1962 (Box 405)
  - Narcotics, 1953-1954 (Box 405)
  - Nat, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 405)
  - Nat, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 406)
  - National, 1941-1956; (29 folders) (Box 406)
  - National, 1956-1962; (12 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1949-1950 (Box 407)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1938 (Box 407)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1944-1948; (4 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Citizens Commission for Public Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 407)
  - National Commercial Teachers Federation, 1937-1938 (Box 407)
  - National Committee for Music Appreciation, 1939-1941; (2 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Committee for the Florence Agreement, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Committee on Education, 1937-1938 (Box 407)
  - National Companies, 1941-1942 (Box 407)
  - National Conference on Christians and Jews, 1950-1958; (2 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Conference of College and University Presidents, 1942 (Box 407)
  - National Conference of State University Schools on Business, 1940-1943; (3 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Council of Thespians, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 407)
  - National Defense, 1940-1942; (8 folders) (Box 407)
  - National-Defense Education Act of 1958, 1958, 1960-1962; (3 folders) (Box 408)
    - Educational Television and Radio Center, 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 408)
  - NDEA English and Foreign Language Institute Conference, 1961 (Box 408)
  - National-Educational Television and Radio Center, 1959-1962; (7 folders) (Box 408)
    - Educational Film Service, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 408)
    - Federation of College and University Business Officers Association, 1955-1961; (3 folders) (Box 408)
    - Foundation for the Education in American Citizenship, 1944-1945 (Box 408)
  - National Foundation for the Education in American Citizenship, 1945-1946 (Box 409)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1950-1951 (Box 409)
  - National Health Assembly, 1948 (Box 409)
  - National Housing Agency, 1945-1949; (6 folders) (Box 409)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1958-1959 (Box 409)
  - National Japanese American Student Relocation Council, 1942-1944 (Box 409)
  - National Life Insurance Company, 1958-1959 (Box 409)
  - National Manpower Council, 1957-1958; (2 folders) (Box 409)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1961-1962 (Box 409)
  - National Municipal League, 1939-1948; (12 folders) (Box 409)
  - National Research Council, 1937-1962; (15 folders) (Box 409)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 409)
  - National Science Foundation, 1954-1961; (8 folders) (Box 410)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students (Box 410)
  - National Self Government Committee, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 410)
  - National Student Employment Committee, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 410)
  - National Student Federation (Box 410)
  - National Theatre Conference, 1947-1948 (Box 410)
  - National Thrift Committee, 1948-1958; (8 folders) (Box 410)
  - National Thrift Committee, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 411)
  - National Youth Administration, 1937-1940; (26 folders) (Box 411)
  - National Youth Administration, 1939-1946; (48 folders) (Box 412)
  - Naval Training School for Storekeepers, 1942-1943; (2 folders) (Box 413)
  - Naval Training School for Storekeepers - Women / WAVES (Box 413)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 413)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 413)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 413)
  - Naval Training School, 1942-1945; (8 folders) (Box 413)
  - Naval Training Station, 1943-1944 (Box 413)
  - Naval Yeoman School - Cooks and bakers training, 1942-1943 (Box 413)
  - Navy Housing, 1942-1943 (Box 413)
  - Navy League of the United States, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 413)
  - Navy Photographic School Possibility, 1941-1942 (Box 413)
  - Ne, 1937-1954; (16 folders) (Box 413)
  - Ne, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 414)
  - Nea, 1946-1947 (Box 414)
  - Neal, Marcellus, 1939-1940 (Box 414)
  - Nebraska University, 1938-1953; (16 folders) (Box 414)
  - Nef, 1948-1949 (Box 414)
  - Neff, F.R., 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 414)
  - Negro, 1937-1962 (Box 414)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 414)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 414)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 414)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 414)
    - Negro materials used by HBW, 1940-1941 (Box 414)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 414)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 414)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 414)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 414)
      (Includes "The Negro in America" by Maxwell S. Stewart)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 414)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 414)
    - Negro situation on campus - Mr. Franklin's file, 1946-1947 (Box 414)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 414)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 414)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 414)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 414)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 414)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 414)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 414)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 414)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 414)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 414)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 414)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 414)
  - Negro Beauty Queen, 1959 (Box 414)
  - Negro Housing (Box 414)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 414)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 414)
    - Non-Segregation Bill, 1948-1949 (Box 414)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 414)
    - Petition re: houses leased for Negro students, 1942-1943 (Box 414)
    - Negro Housing, newspaper clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 414)
  - Negroes and Jews Statistics of, 1940-1941 (Box 414)
    - (Folder 1) (Box 414)
    - (Folder 2) (Box 414)
  - Negro, practice teaching, 1942-1943 (Box 414)
  - Negro Question, 1938-1940 (Box 414)
  - Nel, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 414)
  - Nel, 1955-1962; (17 folders) (Box 415)
  - Nelson, Mrs. Alice, 1937-1957 (Box 415)
    (18 files)
  - Nelson, James B., 1937-1948; (8 folders) (Box 415)
  - Nem, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 415)
  - Nepotism, 1947-1948 (Box 415)
  - Nepotism Rulings, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 415)
  - Nettl, Paul, 1944-1959 (Box 415)
  - Neuman, Georg, 1941-1942; (2 folders) (Box 415)
  - New, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 415)
  - New, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 416)
  - New Albany Schools, 1943-1944 (Box 416)
  - New Courses, 1948-1949 (Box 416)
  - Newcomen Society, 1944-1962; (18 folders) (Box 416)
  - New Harmony Commission, 1939-1941 (Box 416)
  - New Harmony Commission, 1941-1956; (17 folders) (Box 417)
  - Newkirk, Bess, 1938-1939 (Box 417)
  - Newm, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 417)
  - New Mexico (Box 417)
  - New School for Social Research, 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 417)
  - New Student Testing and Allied Functions Department of Psychology, 1937-1938 (Box 417)
  - New York, 1947-1951 (Box 417)
    - New York City, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 417)
    - New York State, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 417)
    - New York City Broadway Plays, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 417)
    - New York Folder, 1939-1940 (Box 417)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1938-1939 (Box 417)
    - New York Times, 1944-1956; (12 folders) (Box 417)
    - New York University, 1937-1938 (Box 417)
    - New York Times, 1956-1962; (7 folders) (Box 417)
    - New York University, New York City, 1938-1945; (9 folders) (Box 417)
  - New York University, New York City, 1945-1962; (16 folders) (Box 418)
  - New York University, Albany, 1943-1953; (9 folders) (Box 418)
  - New York University Hall of Fame, 1950-1951; (2 folders) (Box 418)
    - Susan B. Anthony, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Alexander Graham Bell, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Elizabeth Blackwell, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Clara Barton, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Dorothea Lynd Dix, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - William Crawford Gorgas, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - John Gorrie, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Thomas J. (Stonewall) Jackson, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Samuel Charles Mazzuchelli, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Lucretta Mott, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Charles Sanders Pierce, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Henry Martyn Robert, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Elizabeth Cady Stanton, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Zachary Taylor, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - Horace Wells, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
    - George Westinghouse, 1950-1951 (Box 418)
  - New York University Hall of Fame, 1951-1962; (27 folders) (Box 418)
  - News Bureau, 1937-1962; (27 folders) (Box 419)
  - News Bureau, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 420)
  - Newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 420)
  - Ni, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 420)
  - Nigerian Project Miscellaneous (Box 420)
  - Nie, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 420)
  - Night Work Permits, 1945-1949; (4 folders0 (Box 420)
  - Nik, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 420)
  - No, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 420)
  - No, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 421)
  - Nolan, Val, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 421)
  - Non-Partisan Committee for Peace Through Revision of the Neutrality Law, 1939-1940 (Box 421)
  - Non-Resident Students, 1938-1939 (Box 421)
  - Nor, 1937-1960; (23 folders) (Box 421)
  - Nor, 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 422)
  - NCAGU, 1937-1945; (5 folders) (Box 422)
  - Normal College of the American Gymnastic Union of Indiana University, 1937-1959; (25 folders) (Box 422)
  - Norman, Hugh W., 1939-1957; (9 folders) (Box 422)
  - Norris, Howard K., 1939-1940 (Box 422)
  - North Carolina-Bankers Conference, 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 422)
    - University of North Carolina, 1937-1938 (Box 422)
  - North Dakota University, 1937-1953; (15 folders) (Box 422)
  - Northern Indiana Children's Hospital, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 422)
  - Northern Regional Research Laboratory, 1939-1940 (Box 422)
  - Northwest Territory Celebration Commission, 1937-1938 (Box 422)
  - Northwestern University, 1937-1949; (12 folders) (Box 422)
  - Northwestern University, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 423)
  - Norton, E.T.-Quartette, 1938-1939 (Box 423)
  - Norville, Professor Lee, 1937-1953; (15 folders) (Box 423)
  - Norways Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 423)
  - Not, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 423)
  - Notre Dame University, 1937-1953; (16 folders) (Box 423)
  - Nov, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 423)
  - Noyes, Russell, 1940-1954; (15 folders) (Box 423)
  - Noyes Scholarship, 1937-1939; (3 folders) (Box 423)
  - Noyes, La Verne, 1938-1940; (7 folders) (Box 423)
  - Noyes, La Verne, 1939-1943; (7 folders) (Box 424)
  - Nu, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 424)
  - Nuclear Physics Conference, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 424)
  - Nurnberger, Dr. Care E., 1939-1940 (Box 424)
  - Nursery and Child Care Facilities (Box 424)
  - Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Advisory Board for Public Health Nursing (Box 424)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 424)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 424)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 424)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 424)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Advisory Committee for Advanced Nursing Education Program Meeting, October 24, 1947; 1947-1948 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Advisory Board for Public Health Nursing, 1948-1949 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Advisory Committee to the Division of Nursing Education (Box 424)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. Advisory Committee to the Division of Nursing Education (Box 424)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 424)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 424)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 424)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 424)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 424)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 424)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Indiana Committee on Nursing for the Future, 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Conference Related to Pre-Nursing Courses, 1947-1948 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Curriculum, 1942-1943 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Education (Box 424)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 424)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 424)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. School of Education (Box 424)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 424)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 424)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 424)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. Assoc. of Collegiate Schools of Nursing. Survey, 1946-1947 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. School of Education, 1947-1948 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. School of Education. Report of Survey of Nursing Service Dept. of the Hospitals at the I.U. Medical Centert, 1948-1949 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. School of Education (Box 424)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 424)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Education Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Education Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing Education, 1949-1950 (Box 424)
  - Nursing. Nursing Education. School of Education (Box 425)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 425)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 425)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 425)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 425)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 425)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 425)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 425)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 425)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 425)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 425)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, School of. Self-Evaluation Report, 1960 (Box 425)
  - School of Nursing, Annual Report (Box 425)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 425)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, School of. Report of Nursing Education, 1962 (Box 425)
  - Nursing Education, Enrollment (Box 425)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 425)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 425)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 425)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 425)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 425)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 425)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 425)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 425)
  - Nursing Education, Other Schools (Box 425)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 425)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 425)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 425)
  - Financial Problems of School of Nursing (Box 425)
  - Nurses, Practical Training (Box 425)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 425)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 425)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 425)
  - Nursing Situation, 1942-1943 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, Nurses Training Act (Bolton Bill), 1943-1944 (Box 425)
  - Nurses Training, Miscellaneous (Box 425)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 425)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 425)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 425)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 425)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 425)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 425)
    - 1950 (Box 425)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 425)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 425)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 425)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 425)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 425)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 425)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 425)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, Training School for Nurses (Indianapolis) (Box 425)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 425)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 425)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, Training School for Nurses, Addition (Box 425)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 425)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 425)
  - Nursing, Training School for Nurses (Indianapolis) (Box 425)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 425)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 425)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 425)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 425)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 425)
    - 1951 (Box 425)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 425)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 425)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 425)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 425)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 425)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 425)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 425)
  - O, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 425)
  - O, 1946-1962; (15 folders) (Box 426)
  - Invitations, 1942-1943; (3 folders) (Box 426)
  - Miscellaneous, 1942-1943 (Box 426)
  - Oakleaf Lincoln Collection, 1942-1943; (2 folders) (Box 426)
  - Oaths, 1951-1952 (Box 426)
  - Ob, 1937-1950; (7 folders) (Box 426)
  - O'Bannon, Maurice, 1946-1947 (Box 426)
  - Oberlander Trust, 1939-1940 (Box 426)
  - Oberlin College, 1937-1947; (9 folders) (Box 426)
  - Oc, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 427)
  - Od, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 427)
  - Oe, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 427)
  - Office Equipment, 1947-1962; (13 folders) (Box 427)
  - Official Equipment, 1948-1949 (Box 427)
  - Office of Military Information, 1947-1948 (Box 427)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1958-1959 (Box 427)
  - Office of Veteran's Affairs, 1944-1945 (Box 427)
  - Office of Procedure Guide, 1946-1947 (Box 427)
  - Officers Reserve Corps, 1946-1947 (Box 427)
  - Office Supplies, 1943-1944 (Box 427)
  - Officer's Training, 1942-1943 (Box 427)
  - Official University Guests, 1954-1961; (12 folders) (Box 427)
  - Og, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 427)
  - Oh, 1942-1955; (12 folders) (Box 427)
  - O'Hara, Father John, 1937-1938 (Box 427)
  - O'Harrow, Dennis, 1937-1938 (Box 427)
  - Ohio State University, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 427)
  - Ohio State University, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 428)
  - Ohio State, 1937-1949; (12 folders) (Box 428)
  - Ohio Wesleyan University, 1939-1949; (10 folders) (Box 428)
  - Oil Conference, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 428)
  - Oklahoma, University of, 1939-1953; (14 folders) (Box 428)
  - Ol, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 428)
  - Old Trails Building, 1947-1948 (Box 428)
  - Oli, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 428)
  - Olmsted, Mrs. Joanna, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 428)
  - Ols, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 428)
  - Om, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 428)
  - Omega Psi Phi, 1952-1958 (Box 428)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa Fraternity, 1938-1939 (Box 428)
  - Omnibus Education Bill, 1960-1961 (Box 428)
  - On, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 428)
  - On, 1948-1949 (Box 429)
  - Opera Supper and Guests, 1942 (Box 429)
  - Optometry, 1945-1962; (27 folders) (Box 429)
  - Or, 1937-1958; (21 folders) (Box 429)
  - Or, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 430)
  - Orchestra National Cultural Program, 1948-1949 (Box 430)
  - Organizational Charts (Box 430)
  - Orientation Program, 1939-1941; (3 folders) (Box 430)
  - Orientation Center, 1958-1959 (Box 430)
  - Os, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 430)
  - Osborn Engineering Company, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 430)
  - Ot, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 430)
  - Ou, 1938-1941; (4 folders) (Box 430)
  - Outstanding Fields, 1953-1954 (Box 430)
  - Outside Speakers, 1939-1940 (Box 430)
  - Ov, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 430)
  - Ow, 1944-1955; (11 folders) (Box 430)
  - Owen, Mary Bess, 1938-1948; (2 folders) (Box 430)
  - P, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 431)
  - Pakistan (Box 431)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 431)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 431)
    - BMSI, 1958-1959 (Box 431)
    - BMSI Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 431)
  - Pakistan-BMSI, 1958-1959 (Box 432)
    - ICA Contract, 1955-1962; (6 folders) (Box 432)
    - Project, 1958-1959 (Box 432)
  - Pal, 1943-1962; (21 folders) (Box 432)
  - Palakawongsa, Nob, 1960 (Box 432)
  - Pan, 1937-1955; (11 folders) (Box 432)
  - Panday, Ramnarase, 1948-1955 (Box 432)
  - Panhellenic Association I.U. Rush Rules, etc., 1937-1938 (Box 432)
  - Panienska, Irene, 1947-1948 (Box 432)
  - Par, 1937-1957; (20 folders) (Box 432)
  - Par, 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 433)
  - Parents' Day, 1939-1941; (2 folders) (Box 433)
  - Park, 1937-1955; (6 folders) (Box 433)
  - Parking, 1940-1941 (Box 433)
  - Parr, 1937-1948; (5 folders) (Box 433)
  - Pas, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 433)
  - Pat, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 433)
  - Patent policy, correspondence with other schools regarding, 1940 (Box 433)
  - Patrick, J.E., 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 433)
  - Patten Foundation Lectures, etc. (Box 433)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 433)
    - Pearl, Raymond, 1938-1939 (Box 433)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 433)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 433)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 433)
    - Copyright matters, 1942-1943 (Box 433)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 433)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 433)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 433)
    - Gilberto Freyre lectures, 1945-1946 (Box 433)
    - Raymond Pearl lectures, 1945-1946 (Box 433)
    - Herbert Feis lectures, 1945-1946 (Box 433)
    - Herbert V. Evatt lectures, 1945-1946 (Box 433)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 433)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 433)
  - Patten Foundation, 1937-1962; (37 folders) (Box 434)
  - Patten, Will T., 1936-1937 (Box 434)
  - Patterson, Richard C., Jr., 1938-1939 (Box 434)
  - Patton, Ottis, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 434)
  - Patty, W.W., 1941-1959; (19 folders) (Box 434)
  - Pau, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 434)
  - Pay, 1947-1955; (5 folders) (Box 434)
  - Payne, Dean F., 1937-1942; (8 folders) (Box 434)
  - Payne, Dean F., 1941-1953; (13 folders) (Box 435)
  - Pe, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 435)
  - Pea, 1952-1953 (Box 435)
  - Peace Corps, 1961-1962 (Box 435)
  - Pearson, Henry E., 1937-1938 (Box 435)
  - Pearson, Henry E., 1938-1959; (27 folders) (Box 436)
  - Pec, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 436)
  - Pec, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 437)